MUHAMMAD RIZQI RAHMATULLAH

089730814733 | muhammad.120130073@student.itera.ac.id | http://www.linkedin.com/in/rizqi-rahmatullah-4ba64b24b

Palembang, Sumatera Selatan

I am a curious learner. I am the type of person who always want to know something new and want to make a lot of experience in electricity. I enjoy learn about electrical system control and robotics. I had done a lot of projects about Arduino programming that's made me good in team work and become person that creative, discipline, and persistent. I enjoy on supportive and open-minded environment for my maximal performance. Also, I am looking forward to improve myself to make a grater impact to my environment. "To be a great person, must pass through heavy obstacles".

Work Experiences

Chemistry laboratory - ITERA, Lampung Selatan

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

Chemistry practicum assistant

A room in which there are chemical equipment's are used for experiments. In Laboratory there is a person who take care of it, that person called lab assistant. therefore if there is a chemistry practice the room will be used

- I do mentoring about chemistry experiments spanning more than 50 individuals
- I succeed teaching all of the participants

Elictrical Laboratory - ITERA, Lampung Selatan

Aug 2022 - Present

Laboratory assistant

Electrical Engineering Laboratory helps student to learn about basics and principle of Electrical Engineering. This lab has already equipped measurement and monitoring device, therefore student can learn in that laboratory to improve his electricity skills

- I do mentoring about chemistry experiments spanning more than 80 individuals
- · I succeed teaching all of the participants

Education Level

Institut Teknologi Sumatera 📀 - Lampung Selatan, Indonesia

Aug 2020 - Aug 2024 (Expected)

Bachelor Degree in Electrical Engineering, 3.44/4.00

- Current GPA 3.44
- Community service volunteer from the Electrical Engineering department to create and educate the use of solar panels to turn on street lights in Desa Sindang Anom Lampung Timur District
- Member of Division Arduino Training at Unit Robotica in ITERA (2021-2022)
- Head of Human Resource Department at Sriwijaya ITERA (2021-2022)
- Staff of Media and Informatic Department at Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro in ITERA (2021-2022)
- Community service volunteer from the Electrical Engineering department to educate about basic ultrasonic sensor and RC controller for elementary and junior high school
- Participant public workshop about "What Company Looks In You (Interview 101)" organized by XL Axiata Future Leaders (2021)
- Particpant national public workshop about "Harmonisasi Dalam Pandemi Untuk Berinovasi" organized by Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro Universitas Sebelas Maret (2021)
- Participant national public workshop about "Power System Competition" organized by "Menyongsong Digitalisasi Sistem
 Ketenagalistrikan Indonesia Di Era Industri 4.0" organized by Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro Universitas Gadjah Mada (2021)

SMA Negeri 6 Palembang @ - Palembang, Indonesia

Aug 2017 - Aug 2020

High School Diploma in IPA

- Member of Rohis Ukhuwah (2017-2019)
- Head of human resource development Da'i (2018-2019)
- Member of Soccer of Six (2017-2019)
- Member of scientific group (2017-2019)

Organisational Experience

Sriwijaya ITERA - ITERA, Lampung Selatan

Feb 2021 - Present

Head of human resource department

Sriwijaya ITERA is community that accommodates people of South Sumatra in ITERA

 Human resource department is department that create new cadres that have responsibility, solidarity and good in manner for regeneration of UKM Sriwijaya ITERA

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro - ITERA, Lampung Selatan

Feb 2021 - Present

Staff of Media and Informatic Department

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro is community that accommodates student of Electrical Engineering in ITERA

• Inform about ITERA electrical engineering either inside or outside ITERA. What I am doing is creating an article about Electrical Engineering

Unit Robotica ITERA - ITERA, Lampung Selatan

Feb 2021 - Present

Member of Division Arduino Training

Unit Robotica ITERA (UROTERA) is part of the ITERA student activity unit which houses robotics enthusiasts

• Learn about arduino programming and rafting robot

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Webinars Attended ② (2021): Institut Teknologi Sumatera major of Electrical Engineering
- Achievements ❷ (2022): Electrical Engineering ITERA Event
- Soft Skills @ (2022): Pemandu Latihan Keterampilan Manajemen Mahasiswa (LKMM ITERA) Kampus Merdeka